fiskerautomotive.com 2019-04-10

# FiskerInc.com Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us.

It is Fisker Inc.'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

 California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for those entities’ direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge.

 If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 1580 Francisco St. Suite B Torrance, CA 90501. For all requests, you must put the statement “California Privacy Rights Notice” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. You also need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via telephone, email, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

  **California Do Not Track Disclosures**

 California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how a website operator responds to “Do Not Track” (DNT) browser settings. DNT is a feature offered by some browsers which, when enabled, sends a signal to websites to request that your browsing is not tracked, such as by third party ad networks, social networks and analytic companies. We do not currently take actions to respond to DNT signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a DNT standard once one is created. For information about DNT, please visit: [http://www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/)

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Fisker Inc. may change this privacy policy from time to time at Fisker Inc.'s sole discretion. Please check back periodically for changes. You will be able to see that changes have been made by checking to see the effective date posted at the end of the policy.

Last updated October 25th, 2018.
